islandtrends.com 2018-04-06

# Island Trends - Upscale Fashion, Swimwear, Shoes and Sandals for Men and Women

## CONTACT US FOR ASSISTANCE

**Telephone: 1-877-342-8615 or 1-239-963-8564 between 9am & 6pm EST daily **

**Email:[help@islandtrends.com](mailto:help@islandtrends.com) 24 hours a day, 7 days a week**

Island Trends values customer privacy. The requested personal information, including your name, shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, billing address, credit card number, and expiration date will not be sold or traded to mailing list firms. 

Island Trends collects that information in order to: 

\- Process an order   
\- Verify your identity for payment authorization   
\- Contact you regarding your order status   
\- Ship your order to you   
\- Enter you in a sweepstakes (only if you request)   
\- Send you an Island Trends newsletter (only if you request)   
\- Generate anonymous statistics   
\- Provide you with an excellent shopping experience. 

Once Island Trends gathers your name and address, this information will then be transferred to your credit card company, if applicable, for confirmation to complete your purchase. Your shipping information may also be supplied to a third-party fulfillment center (eg UPS), but your name and address will not be used for any other purpose than delivery of your order. Your name and address will not be sold or traded to mailing-list firms.

## Unsubscribing from Newsletters

To opt out of receiving communications from Island Trends, just go to our unsubscribe page and enter the requested information, or email us.

## Updating Your Information

If the personal information Island Trends has gathered from you changes or you no longer desire our service, we will gladly correct, update, or remove any personal data you have previously provided to us. To request a change or removal of your personal information, please contact us.

## Security

Island Trends is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. To protect the information you send from your computer to Island Trends e-commerce system, this information including your credit card number, name, and address is encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software. Internally, we use encryption and Web security technologies to protect the privacy of your personal data. Only parties responsible for processing your order have access to your credit card and bank information. 

Island Trends continuously reviews its policies and practices to ensure that all customer information remains secure. 

## Technology

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer hard drive. You must have cookies enabled in order for you to be able to perform many of the general functions on the Island Trends Web site including the use of our shopping cart. Island Trends does not use cookies to store or collect any personal information such as names, addresses, or payment information. To learn how to enable cookies on your computer, visit the website of your browser's manufacturer.

## Legal Disclaimer

The only time Island Trends will disclose personal information is when required to by law or with the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the law.

If you have questions about this privacy statement, please email the Island Trends customer service department at [help@islandtrends.com](mailto:help@islandtrends.com).
